I was going to watch Mister Doctor but I'm
iba a ver lo de Mister doctor pero me da
a little lazy I'm going to watch it a little
un poco de pereza Voy a verlo un poco
but I can't guarantee that we'll see the
pero no os garantizo que lo veamos
whole thing Uh well I'm seeing that it's half an
entero Eh pues estoy viendo que es media
hour in the end they have reached an agreement or
hora al final han llegado a un acuerdo o
so so so many
sea tanto tanto tantos
tricks to reach an agreement in the end
aleos para llegar a un acuerdo al final
no which is what they should have done
no que es lo que tenan que haber hecho
from the first moment I mean they are
desde el primer momento o sea te están
offering you an agreement and you are there no
ofreciendo un acuerdo y estás tú no la
freedom of expression I don't know what well you do
libertad de expresión la no sé qué pues
n't have to reach an agreement because
no tienes que llegar a un acuerdo porque
you have gone too far with your mouth no more let's
te has pasado con la boca sin más no a
see what it's about today Monday the
ver de qué trata el día de hoy el lunes
3rd Monday March 3rd
3 de lunes 3 de marzo del
2025 at 10:40 pm I can tell you,
2025 siendo las 10:40 pm les puedo decir
Octavia Ryo better known as Mr.
yo octavia ryo mejor conocido como Mr
Doctor that uh the complaint
doctor que eh se ha anulado la denuncia
by Marifer Centeno against me has been annulled
por parte de Marifer Centeno hacia un
both Marifer Centeno, a well-known
servidor tanto Marifer Centeno conocida
graphologist in the middle of the show and me We
grafólogo en el medio del espectáculo y
have reached an agreement
un servidor Hemos llegado a un acuerdo
in which the
en el cual se ha finiquitado la la
complaint has been finalized and this would not have been possible
denuncia y esto no hubiera sido posible
without the intervention of one of the
sin la intervención de uno de los
best lawyers in this country, one of the
mejores abogados de este país de uno de
best litigating lawyers  that this
los mejores abogados litigantes que esta
time I'm not litigating that this time he wasn't on
vez no litigo que esta vez no estuvo de
anyone's side but rather he was a
lado de nadie sino más bien fue un
mediator a person who came to bring
mediador una persona que llegó a poner
balance and I'm talking about Eric
equilibrio y estoy hablando de Eric
Rauda I want to start by thanking him
rauda quiero empezar agradeciéndole a él
because without his intervention this
porque sin su intervención esto no
would not have been possible one of the
hubiera sido posible uno de los eh
conflicts that most uh fueled
conflictos con los que más eh se avivó
the Mexican citizenry and several other
la ciudadanía mexicana y de varios otros
countries finally came to an end and as
países por fin llegó a a su fin y como
Eric Rauda said a couple of minutes ago in a video uh that many
un video Eric rauda eh que muchos lo
remember for having been at the time
recuerdan por haber sido en su momento
the lawyer for Fofo Márquez and having been the
el abogado del fofo Márquez en haber
lawyer for Paola Dorante
estado ser abogado de Paola dorante
and in the case of Paco Stanley he this time
e y el caso de Paco Stanley él esta vez
was the one who helped us mediate and
fue quien nos nos ayudó a mediar y a
reach a solution
llegar a una a una solución
uh as he he said many knew it should have been
eh como él él lo decía muchos se se
reached from the first
tenía que haber llegado desde el primer
moment it wasn't necessary so much but well they
momento no hacía falta tanto pero bueno
suddenly hope that one of the two
esperan de pronto que una de las dos
parties wins that one of the two parties
partes gane que una de las dos partes
triumphs and that in the end it ends Does
triunfe y que al final se termine
anyone know the minute in which we can
Alguien sabe el minuto en el que podemos
see what the agreement is and a battle
ver cuál es el acuerdo and una batalla
uh the minute
eh el minuto
uh where both parties wore us down the
eh donde nos desgaste ambas partes la
reality is that we were already quite
realidad es que ya estábamos bastante
worn out And that had not happened at the
desgastados Y eso que no había ocurrido
hearing the first hearing
la la audiencia la primera audiencia
But fortunately and thanks I insist to
Pero afortunadamente y gracias insisto a
Eric Rauda and also to the disposition of
Eric rauda y también a la disposición de
Marifer this came to an end eh
Marifer esto llegó a un a a un fin eh
As Eric also said eh in his
Como lo dijo también Eric eh en su
statement you can go see it on all his
comunicado pueden ir a verlo a todas sus
social networks it is a statement of a
redes sociales es un comunicado de un
minute and a half or almost two eh There are
minuto y medio o casi dos eh Hay
agreements that were signed they were signed
acuerdos que se firmaron se firmaron el
today there in the offices of
día de hoy allá en las oficinas de de
Eric Rauda
Eric rauda
eh agreements were reached
eh se llegaron acuerdos se llegaron a
agreements eh in which he has paid let's go, he has
convenios eh en que le ha pagado vamos
paid which
que le ha pagado los cuales pues
obviously eh Neither she Marifer nor I
obviamente eh Ni tanto ella Marifer como
were going to be in complete
un servidor íbamos a estar completamente
agreement But in the end the most
de acuerdos Pero al final lo más
important thing was to have peace and as I know it is
importante era tener paz y como bien Se
said this is a mediation This
se se dice esto es un una mediación Este
is a point Well, in which a middle point is sought
es un punto Pues que se busca un punto
in which although both parties will not be
medio en el cual si bien ambas partes no
completely satisfied
van a quedar completamente conformes
because well both parties have
porque pues ambas ambas partes hemos
lost peace of mind money
perdido tranquilidad dinero
eh well, eh above all peace, I think in the
eh pues eh sobre todo paz creo yo al
end it was achieved eh this this
final se logró pues eh esta esta
mediation it was possible to reach an agreement
mediación se logró llegar a un acuerdo
eh host
eh [__]
Look host Look it has been in code 10
Mira [__] Mira ha estado en código 10
today José Manuel we would have seen each other
hoy José Manuel nos hubiéramos visto el
Kira's dad was there we
papá de Kira
would have seen each other
estaba nos hubiéramos visto
you What a coincidence right
tú Qué casualidad verdad
Oh tomorrow I'll see what he
Oh mañana lo veré a ver qué ha
said I talked to Marifer we
contado yo platiqué con Marifer
were talking we fixed our
estuvimos platicando arreglamos nuestra
at minute 29 don't
en el minuto 29 no me
[ __ ] with me [ __ ] let's see what I want to find out I
jodas cabrón a ver que me quiero enterar
lost the minute I was going for man you know what he puts in
he perdido el minuto por el que iba tío
half an hour for this
saes que le mete media hora para este
roll man tell me I had to pay him
rollo tío dime le he tenido que pagar
How much let's see Ah It's true candr will have
Cuánto a ver Ah Es verdad candr lo habrá
summarized it not
resumido no
controversial agreement Marifer Centeno and Mr.
polémico acuerdo Marifer Centeno y Mr
doctor have just uploaded controversial videos
doctor acaban de subir polémicos videos
both reveal that the legal battle has come
ambos revelan que la batalla legal llegó
to an end Mr. doctor said that he is going to
a su fin ya Mr doctor dijo que va a
upload a video apologizing and give
subir un video pidiendo disculpas y dará
several press conferences while he
varias conferencias de prensa mientras
has to upload a video
que tiene que subir un vídeo pidiendo
apologizing and giving press conferences
disculpas y dando conferencias de prensa
okay I understand that by the ways no, it is not going to go, he is
vale entiendo que por las formas no no
not going to withdraw the criticism noer
va no va a retirar la crítica noer
Centeno shares a publication deletes
Centeno comparte una publicación elimina
a video that he had uploaded at dawn and
un video que había subido de madrugada y
not only that it is possibly in the house
no solo eso posiblemente esté en la casa
of the famous three it was the lawyer Eric
de los famosos tres fue el abogado Eric
rauda who revealed that he himself contacted
rauda quien reveló que él mismo contactó
the two to Finally end all
a los dos para Ya por fin terminar todo
this we know that they had  that to sign a
esto sabemos que tuvieron que firmar un
confidential document however Mr.
documento confidencial sin embargo Mr
doctor made new revelations Marifer the
doctor hizo nuevas revelaciones Marifer
same and users are already
igual y ya los usuarios están
interpreting everything below I
interpretando todo a continuación Les
bring you a special capsule with this
traigo una cápsula especial con este
topic that apparently the
tema que al parecer ha terminado el
conflict between Marifer Centeno and Mr.
conflicto entre Marifer Centeno y Mr
doctor is over tomorrow I
doctor ha terminado yo mañana ya a
will extend a public apology to
detalle extenderé una disculpa pública a
Marifer in detail we reached a
Marifer llegamos a una a una
conciliation Prepare yourselves because the orca of
conciliación Prepárense porque laorca de
medicine has not
la medicina no se ha
left What the [ __ ] are you going to do
ido Qué [__] van a
guys it's early in the morning when I
hacer chicos es de madrugada cuando les
'm recording this video and it is that both
estoy grabando este video y es que ambos
content creators and
creadores de contenidos y figuras
public figures revealed to us this long live
públicas nos revelaron est viva la
freedom damn Well but it happens that he has had an
libertad [__] Bueno pero pasa que ha
opinion about heo according to what happened he said
opinado de heo según pasa que ha dicho
after his defense no but the
después de su defensa no pero ya los
media is already covering it
medios de comunicación hacen cobertura
please see the headline of publimetro
por favor vean el titular de publimetro
Marifer Centeno's legal battle
termina la batalla legal de Marifer
against Mr. doctor ends this Monday it was
Centeno contra Mr doctor este lunes se
announced that the influencers reached
anunció que los influencers llegaron a
an out-of-court settlement in this other
un acuerdo extrajudicial en este otro
media for example the graphic says
medio por ejemplo el gráfico dice
Marifer Centeno versus Mr. doctor the
Marifer Centeno versus Mr doctor la
war comes to an end after reaching an
guerra llega a su fin tras llegar a un
agreement here I am leaving you the profile
acuerdo aquí les estoy dejando el perfil
of the lawyer Eric Rueda he is quite well
del abogado Eric Rueda es bastante
known in the media since on the one hand he
conocido en el medio ya que por un lado
participated in the case of  Paco Stanley was
participó en el caso de Paco Stanley fue
Paola's lawyer during also
el abogado de Paola durante también
assumed the defense of fofo Márquez
asumió la defensa de fofo Márquez antes
before his family decided to change
de que su familia decida cambiar de
lawyers now he has been in charge of
abogados ahora ha sido el encargado de
mediating this case that has been
mediar este caso que ya se viene
fought for more than TR months
peleando desde hace más de TR meses
both decided to sign an agreement that
ambos decidieron firmar un convenio que
concludes In short, this
da por concluido En definitiva este
conflict that grew exponentially
conflicto que creció exponencialmente
the specific terms of this
los términos específicos de este
agreement I cannot reveal because they are
convenio no los puedo revelar porque son
confidential I know that many of you
confidenciales sé que muchos de ustedes
want Well there will be money here I imagine and
quer Pues aquí habrá dinero me imagino y
and the money
y el dinero
well It will be secret and it will not be known F
pues Pues será secreto y no se sabrá F
Javi they won but you lost
Javi ganaron ellos pero perdiste tu
because now the almond head is going to
porque ahora sí el cabeza de almendra va
come back to you 100% XD By the way I
a volver contigo al 100 XD Por cierto te
sent you a clip that Lina wanted you to
mandé un clip que Lina quería que
react and a thread of
reaccionaras y un hilo de
serene Of course of course now he is going to
serene Claro que claro que ahora va a
come back Of course here it is going to
volver Claro ya aquí se le va a ir
end a different outcome where
acabando un desenlace diferente donde
one will destroy the other and they are going to feel
uno destruyera al otro y se van a sentir
disappointed angry frustrated by
decepcionados enojados frustrados por
this determination but the work as a
esta determinación pero la labor como
lawyer is not to fuel the war but to
abogado no es alimentar la guerra sino
contribute to the solution among the
aportar a la solución entre las
revelations that he makes to us here a brief
revelaciones que nos hace acá un breve
summary first what I told you at the
resumen primero lo que les decía al
beginning that this is not
comienzo que esto no es de la noche a la
overnight they have been meeting for a
mañana se vienen reuniendo desde hace
while second that there is a document that
tiempo segundo que hay un documento que
both parties signed and that both
ambas partes firmaron y que ambos no
are not 100% in agreement with what it says
están 100% de acuerdo con lo que dice
but for the greater good to not continue
pero por el bien mayor para no seguir
this fight and not continue prolonging it
esta pelea y no seguir alargando
they had to give in in this in the end in
tuvieron que ceder en esta al final en
these agreements what we have to find is
estos acuerdos lo que hay que buscar es
the way that both are as best as
la forma de de que ambos queden lo mejor
possible so that it is not humiliating for
posible que no sea humillante para
either of the two parties not something good
ninguna de las dos partes no algo bien
occasion it required the courage to
ocasión se requirió de la valentía de
sit face to face to argue in a
sentarse frente a frente a alogar de una
reasonable and humane way Marifer and Mr.
manera razonable y humana Marifer y Mr
doctor achieved what seemed impossible
doctor lograron lo que parecía imposible
with great responsibility they left
con mucha responsabilidad dejaron atrás
the confrontation behind and look for a
el enfrentamiento y buscar una solución
constructive solution it is in the most
constructiva es en los momentos más
complex moments where we can notice the value
complejos donde podemos notar el valor
of each person they were days of hard
de cada persona fueron días de mucho
work they were very intense days
trabajo fueron días Muy intensos en
where my job was to be a bridge not a
donde mi labor fue ser un puente no un
wall reveals that this agreement is
muro revela que este acuerdo es
confidential but I have already seen the video that
confidencial pero ya vi el video que
Mr. doctor uploaded a half hour live
subió Mr doctor un en vivo de media hora
and a video that Marifer Centeno uploaded
y un video que subió Marifer Centeno
where they revealed a little bit of what it is
donde nos revelaron un poco de qué se
about I will tell you more later and
trata les voy a decir más adelante y
also Eric Rueda recognizes that
también Eric Rueda reconoce que las
people wanted this fight to continue
personas querían que esta pelea siga
until the end for the  well, major but
hasta el final por el bien mayor pero
both were already tired,
que ya ambos estaban cansados
worn out. Yes, I think it would be time to pay,
desgastados Sí yo creo que tocaría pagar
eh, I think it would be time to pay, what's the point of it
eh yo creo que tocaría pagar qué sentido
being confidential? Let's see
tiene que sea confidencial vamos a ver
if it has to, if it has to, if it has to, if it has to
si si tiene que si tiene que si tiene
upload an apology video and she's
que subir un vídeo de disculpas y y ella
going to upload something too, we don't know
va a subir algo también no sabemos el
what tomorrow we
qué mañana lo
'll see. I understand, eh, what's
veremos entiendo eh
left, is it
que que que es lo que queda que sea
confidential? Why does it have to be
confidencial por qué tiene que ser
confidential? Because it's money, of course. I
confidencial pues porque es dinero claro
mean, why would it be confidential? If you ca
o sea por qué iba a ser confidencial si
n't think of anything else that I
no se os ocurre otra cosa que yo ahora
don't have fresh in my head right now, my friends, that it
mismo no la tenga fresca mis panas que
would be
iba a ser
confidential? There isn't any money, there isn't any, there's nothing
confidencial dinero es que no hay no hay
else.
no hay otra cosa